

(naukri.co





Highest Degree: MBA/PGDM [e business]

Current Company: Tata Technologies

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Pune

Current Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Verified : Number | Email - id

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: AWAD Lead, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Application Programming, Software Development, Project Execution, Delivery Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Release Management, ConfigurationManagement, Solution Architecture, Stakeholder Management, Net

Last Active: 23-Jan-21

Last Modified: 23-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

An accomplished professional offering 14+ years of versatile experience in Application Delivery/Management, Project Execution, Solution Designing, ITIL Management and People Management with proven initiatives in executing & completing projects with 100% quality & accuracy Currently working as AD/AM Lead with Tata Technologies Ltd.; leading a highly skilled team of 4 Professionals for leading end-to-end completion of multiple projects (from proposal preparation to delivery) which includes "Unified Medical Benefit Scheme", "Performance Management System", & "Application Maintenance & Application Development" & so on Award-winning professional, acknowledged as Champion of the Quarter in Q2 2017 for delivery of UMBS project independently in shortest time Front-led diverse level of activities which includes: o Hardware provisioning,getting required network port opened from infra team, site configuration in IIS (with dependency

management), change management.

Work Experience

Tata Technologies Ltd as AM and AD Lead Jul 2007 to Jul 2007

Application development and maintenance.

- Tata Technologies as Project Leader Jul 2007 to Till Date
- Aurasoft Technologies Solutions as Software Programmer Jun 2006 to Jul 2007

Software Programmer, worked on two major projects like Indian Army EME.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Sipna Shikshan Prasarak Mandals College of Engineering & Technology Amravati Amravati in 2006

PG: MBA/PGDM (e business) from LN Welingkar Institute of Management Mumbai in 2014

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Diploma in Electronics & Communication Engineering

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Oracle, MySql, SQL Server 2012	
AWS EC2, S3	
ADO.Net, Classic ASP, ASP. Net, C#,	
CSS, HTML, Javascript, XML	
Cordys BOP4, M/C	
IIS 6/7/8	
Sharepoint online	
Remedy 8.1.	
Aditaas	
Rational Clearcase, TFS	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent
Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.